marketinggum.com 2013-10-09

# Privacy Policy | MarketingGum.com

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

### Contact & Address Information

For efficient communication please email us directly at [info@marketinggum.com](mailto:info@marketinggum.com) or contact us by telephone (+64 9 950 3824).

**You can send mail directly to the following postal address:  
**Marketing Gum  
PO Box 300770  
Albany  
Auckland 0752  
NEW ZEALAND

**Physical address:**  
6 Cebel Place  
Rosedale  
Auckland 0632  
NEW ZEALAND
